<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recipe_App</string>
    <string name="recipe_name">Recipe Name</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="ingredients_name">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="instruction_name">Instructions</string>
    <string name="veg_burger_ingredients">
        1 cup cooked brown rice* \n
        1 cup raw walnuts (or sub bread crumbs) \n
        1/2 Tbsp avocado oil (plus more for cooking) \n
        1/2 medium white onion (finely diced // 1/2 onion yields    ~3/4 cup) \n
        1 Tbsp each chili powder, cumin powder, and smoked paprika \n
        1/2 tsp each sea salt and black pepper (plus more for coating burgers) \n
        1 Tbsp coconut sugar (or sub organic brown or muscovado sugar) \n
        1 1/2 cups cooked black beans* (well rinsed, drained and patted dry) \n
        1/3 cup panko bread crumbs (if gluten-free, use gluten-free bread crumbs) \n
        3-4 Tbsp vegan BBQ sauce \n
    </string>
    <string name="veg_burger_recipe">
        If your brown rice isn’t cooked yet, start there by following this method for the best results. 
        Otherwise, move onto the next step.
        Heat skillet over medium heat. \n\n
        Once hot, add raw walnuts and toast for 5-7 minutes, stirring frequently, until fragrant and golden brown. 
        Let cool and move onto the next step. \n\n
        In the meantime, heat the same skillet over medium heat. 
        Once hot, add oil and onion. Season with a bit of salt and pepper and sauté for 3-4 minutes, or until onion is fragrant, soft, and translucent. 
        Remove from heat and set aside. \n\n
        Once walnuts are cooled, add to blender or food processor with chili powder, cumin, smoked paprika, salt, pepper and coconut sugar and blend until a fine meal (see photo) is achieved. 
        Set aside. \n\n
        To a large mixing bowl, add drained, dried black beans and mash well with a fork, leaving only a few whole beans (see photo).
        Next add cooked rice, spice-walnut mixture, sautéed onion, panko bread crumbs, BBQ sauce, and mix thoroughly with a wooden spoon for 1-2 minutes, or until a moldable dough forms. 
        If dry, add extra 1-2 Tbsp (amount as original recipe is written // adjust if altering batch size) BBQ sauce. 
        If too wet, add more panko bread crumbs. Taste and adjust seasonings as needed. \n\n
        For larger burgers, divide into 5 patties (1/2 cup in size // amount as original recipe is written), or form 10 smaller burgers (1/4 cup in size // amount as original recipe is written). 
        To help form the patties, line your 1/2 or 1/4 measuring cup with plastic wrap and pack with burger mixture.  \n\n
        Press down to pack firmly, then lift out by the plastic wrap’s edge, and slightly flatten with hands to form a 3/4-inch thick patty. 
        Set on a baking sheet or plate for grilling. \n\n
        If grilling, heat the grill at this time and brush the grill surface with oil to ease cooking. 
        Otherwise, heat the same skillet you used earlier to medium heat. \n\n
        Once skillet is hot, add just enough oil to lightly coat the bottom of your skillet, then add your burgers – only as many as will comfortably fit in the pan. Otherwise, add burgers to the grill and close lid.
        Cook for 3-4 minutes or until well browned on the underside, then flip gently. 
        They aren’t as firm as meat burgers, but will definitely hold their shape. Reduce heat if cooking/browning too quickly. 
        Cook for 3-4 minutes on other side. \n\n
        Remove burgers from heat to let cool slightly, and prepare any other toppings/sides at this time (such as grilling/toasting your buns).
        Serve burgers as is, or on toasted buns with desired toppings. 
        Leftovers keep in the refrigerator for 2-3 days.  \n\n

    </string>
    <string name="egg_roll_ingredients">
        1½ cup All-purpose flour \n
        1 teaspoon Sugar \n
        ½ teaspoon Salt \n
        1 tablespoon Oil \n
        100-110 ml warm water \n
        5 Eggs
        1 large red Onion, thin sliced \n
        1 medium Cucumber, julienne cut \n
        2-3 green Chillies, thin sliced \n
        1 Lemon \n
        5 tablespoons Tomato Ketchup \n
        1 ½ teaspoons Chaat masala (2 pinches for each Egg roll) \n
        1 teaspoon black Salt (1 big pinch for each Egg roll) \n
        5 pinches of Salt (1 pinch to mix with each egg) \n
        Oil for cooking \n
    </string>
    <string name="egg_roll_recipe">
        Measure 1 and ½ cups of all-purpose flour for the dough and add it in a large mixing bowl. \n\n
        Add ½ teaspoon salt, 1 teaspoon sugar into the bowl and mix all the dry ingredients nicely with the help of a spoon.
        Add 1 tablespoon oil into the mixing bowl. \n\n
        Mix the oil nicely and evenly with the help of your hand.
        Add the required amount of warm water in small portions slowly into the mixture and mix it nicely to make a soft dough. 
        For me, it took exactly 110 ml of water. \n\n
        Apply ½ teaspoon of oil over the dough and cover it with a wet kitchen towel or muslin cloth and let it rest for half an hour.
        On the other hand, cut the onions into thin slices and add ½ of a Lemon juice into it. Mix the juice nicely with hand and separate the layers of onions. 
        Keep it aside. \n\n
        Cut the cucumbers into julienne and slice the green chillies and keep them aside.
        After 30 minutes, knead the dough again and divide it into 5 equal portions. Make 5 flat round dough balls for the paratha.
        Take one ball on a rolling board to make paratha but make sure to cover rest of the dough balls with wet cloth.
        Roll the ball to a thin paratha with the help of a rolling pin. Don’t need to bother about the shape for this time.
        Start from the edge of the thin paratha to make small pleats by folding repeatedly. Then swirl the long thick folded paratha to a round disk like pinwheel pizza.
        Repeat the same process with the remaining flat dough balls. Cover them with wet cloth and allow the disks to rest for another 15 minutes.
        Take one swirl disk to roll lachha paratha and cover rest of the dough disks. \n\n
        Put a heavy bottom pan on medium flame and then roll the disk to a thin paratha. No need to apply oil or flour to roll the paratha.
        Drizzle 1 teaspoon of oil into the pan and place the rolled paratha on it. Pour 1 more teaspoon of oil over the paratha and spread it.
        Cook the paratha over medium flame for 1-2 minutes. Cook it till golden brown spots occur. Press the edges of the paratha for extra crisp. Flip the paratha and cook it again for 1-2 minutes.
        In a bowl, break an egg and add a pinch of salt into it. Whisk the mixture nicely and pour it over the paratha. Spread the mixture with a spoon.
        Add 1 teaspoon oil on the edges of the paratha and flip it quickly but carefully. \n\n
        Cook it over medium flame for another minute until the egg gets fried. Add more oil during the time of frying egg if required.
        Transfer the paratha on a flat surface facing the egg side on the top. \n\n
        Add sliced onion (Step 7) on one side of the paratha but leave a gap for wrapping the paratha.
        Add cucumber and green chillies for the filling of the egg roll.
        Squeeze some drops of lemon juice over the salad. \n\n
        Add 1 tablespoon of tomato ketchup over the salad like a thick line.
        Sprinkle 2 pinches of chaat masala and a pinch of black salt over the salad.
        Roll the egg paratha carefully but tightly. \n\n
        Wrap the lower half of the wrap with a piece of paper and tuck the extra paper at the bottom.
        Repeat the whole process with the remaining disks to prepare the egg roll and serve immediately. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="bread_pakora_ingredients">
        4 slices Bread \n
        2 Boiled Ptatoes(approx.200gm) \n
        3 tablespoon Oil \n
        4 medium size Chopped Onion \n
        2 medium size Chopped Tomato \n
        2 medium size Chopped Green Chili \n
        1/2 tablespoon Cumin Powder \n
        1/2 tablespoon Red Chili Powder \n
        2 pinches Garam Masala Powder \n
        A pinch of Baking Soda \n
        Water(1/2 cup + 3 tablespoons) or as needed \n
        1 cup Gram Flour (besan/chickpea flour) \n
        1 tablespoon Rice Flour(optional) \n
        Tomato Ketchup \n
        Salt to taste \n
    </string>
    <string name="bread_pakora_recipe">
        Step 1 Make the mashed potato filling
        For making these yummy bread pakoras, make the potato filling first.
        For the same, wash the potatoes, then put the potatoes in a pressure cooker and add water in it.
        Boil the potatoes till 3-4 whistles and mash them when they are warm, and add chopped coriander leaves, green chilies, 1 teaspoon red chili powder, dry mango powder (amchur) and salt.
        Mix them well. \n\n
        Step 2 Prepare the batter
        Now prepare the besan batter.
        Take a large bowl, and add besan, ajwain, red chili powder, garam masala powder, asafoetida and salt.
        Drizzle a little water and make a smooth batter.
        Check the seasoning and add few drops of oil in the batter and keep it aside. \n\n
        Step 3 Assemble the bread slices
        Now assemble the bread pakora by slicing the bread into triangular slices.
        Apply green chutney (mint and coriander chutney) on one side of triangular bread and apply mashed potato mixture evenly on the bread.
        Cover this slice with another triangular slice.
        Next dip the bread into the batter. \n\n
        Step 4 Deep fry the pakoras and serve hot
        Take a kadhai over medium flame and add some oil.
        Once the oil is hot enough, leave the bread slices from sides.
        Deep fry these dipped bread slices in hot oil on medium flame till crisp and golden brown.
        Enjoy these freshly prepared bread pakoras with sauce along with tea or coffee. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="egg_curry_ingredients">
        5 Hard Boiled Eggs peeled \n
        1 tablespoon Coconut Oil \n
        1 teaspoon Mustard seeds \n
        1 Cinnamon small stick \n
        3 Cardamom pods \n
        5 Peppercorns lightly smashed \n
        2 – 3 Green Chillies slit lengthwise \n
        1 teaspoon Ginger finely chopped or ginger paste \n
        7 Garlic cloves smashed and roughly chopped or garlic paste \n
        2 Onions finely chopped (medium) \n
        3 Tomatoes finely chopped (large) \n
        1/2 teaspoon Turmeric Powder \n
        1 teaspoon Coriander Powder \n
        1/2 teaspoon Chili Powder Red \n
        1/4 cup Tamarind Water See Note 2 \n
        1 cup Thin Coconut Milk See Note 3 \n
        1/2 cup Thick Coconut Milk \n
        8 – 10 Curry Leaves \n
        Salt to taste \n
    </string>
    <string name="egg_cury_recipe">
        In a large pan, heat coconut oil and add mustard seeds, cinnamon, cardamom, peppercorns and green chilies.
        Once everything starts spluttering, add ginger, garlic and onions. \n\n
        Cook till the onions turn soft and translucent and add tomatoes, turmeric powder, coriander powder, chili powder and salt.
        Let the tomatoes cook till they are pulpy and add tamarind water and thin coconut milk.
        Stir and bring this to a boil. Simmer till the gravy reduces slightly and becomes thicker.
        This will take about 5. At this point, add some water if you need to adjust the consistency.
        Adjust seasoning, add curry leaves and pour in the thick coconut milk. Stir a few times, without letting it come to a boil and switch off the flame.
        Drop the eggs in the curry, and cover and let it sit for five minutes before serving. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="chocolate_cake_ingredients">
        butter and flour for coating and dusting the cake pan \n
        3 cups all-purpose flour \n
        3 cups granulated sugar \n
        1 1/2 cups unsweetened cocoa powder \n
        1 tablespoon baking soda \n
        1 1/2 teaspoons baking powder \n
        1 1/2 teaspoons salt \n
        4 large eggs \n
        1 1/2 cups buttermilk \n
        1 1/2 cups warm water \n
        1/2 cup vegetable oil \n
        2 teaspoons vanilla extract \n
    </string>
    <string name="chocolate_cake_recipe">
        Preheat oven to 350 degrees Fahrenheit.
        Butter three 9-inch cake rounds. Dust with flour and tap out the excess. \n\n
        Mix together flour, sugar, cocoa, baking soda, baking powder, and salt in a stand mixer using a low speed until combined.
        Add eggs, buttermilk, warm water, oil, and vanilla. Beat on a medium speed until smooth. This should take just a couple of minutes.
        Divide batter among the three pans. I found that it took just over 3 cups of the batter to divide it evenly. \n\n
        Bake for 30-35 minutes in a 350 degree oven until a toothpick inserted into the center comes out clean.
        Cool on wire racks for 15 minutes and then turn out the cakes onto the racks and allow to cool completely.
        Frost with your favorite frosting and enjoy! \n\n
    </string>
</resources>